attention I'll say attention German sand
is not unconscious by large frying pan
important documents
who's not trouble we how much trouble so
much don't you frown just knuckle down
and knock on wood
what's up doc please help me mr. bugs I
want you to hide this belly your portal
hacking it did wouldn't happen to be the
document stolen from dead poor joy
Menaka now would it
I'm sure you'll be helping a great man
who will with this document make life
wonderful
in America means big deal they'll be
here tonight with the lovely lady a game
unit people I talk to pretty kids
soldier in this man's army they don't
wanna know you love this light ah got
word you had that important document yet
dinner jacket wearing varmint
jiggling a widget he did let's just say
a little birdie told me I want that
paper and I want it now
paper what this paper boy
all gar come later
I demand some service I'll be right back
Chitti dear a with a refresh please play
it for me
I hope you don't mean that knock on wood
song I've got a splitting headache you
know my favorite song I thought I told
you never to play that song me you think
I wanted to play that
kitty-kitty-kitty
where's my dreamboat
of all the juice joints in all the towns
in all the countries in all the oils she
picks this one I know what you mean I
had a girl once she dumped me for
arrested semester general pandemonium
thinks he knows something about that
stone and document I stick my Cottontail
for no one how many times I have to tell
you I don't have that document do you
really expect me to believe that gee
you're having a barbecue and didn't
invite me but out a rabbit am i
interrogating this suspect you're going
about this all wrong
so you're here to Jonny Ryan for
stealing a girl we're on to you
pandemonium so you meet his where he is
I can explain mommy no man who popped my
balloon I'm guilty
mr. slash nose got a plane to catch
boom buggy
now it's Lazlo I have something I think
you're looking for so you have this is
gonna make me rich
box I don't know if I can leave you
again
listen kitty if you don't go women
you'll regret it
in this crazy wild the lives of tree
people don't amount to it yeah yeah
hillock green Silla green sweet oh gotta
go go go